http://www.uncp.edu/about/legal-copyright-privacy

Skip to main content
×
Academic AffairsAcademic and Military OutreachAccessibility Resource CenterAccounts PayableA.D. GalleryADA CoordinatorAdmissionsAdmissions, UndergraduateAdvancementAerospace Studies (Air Force ROTC)Alumni Engagement, Office ofAmerican Indian StudiesArtArts and Sciences, College ofAthletic TrainingAthleticsAuxiliary & Business ServicesBiologyBiotech CenterBookstoreBrave CentralBraveCartBraveCart ShopperStudent Accounts/CashierBusiness, School ofCalendar, AcademicCalendar, UniversityCampus Engagement and LeadershipCampus RecreationCareer CenterCashierCatalog, UniversityCenter for Student SuccessChancellor, Office of theChemistry & PhysicsCollege Opportunity ProgramCommencementCommunity and Civic EngagementControllerCounsel, GeneralCounselingCounseling and Psychological ServicesDining, UniversityDoITEducation, School ofEducational Leadership and SpecialtiesDepartment of Teacher EducationEnglish, Theatre, and Foreign LanguagesEnglish Language InstituteEnrollmentEnvironmental Health and SafetyFacilities ManagementFacilities Reservation SystemFaculty SenateFATE ProgramFinance and AdministrationFinancial AidFinancial Planning and BudgetingFraternity & Sorority LifeGender Studies MinorGeology and GeographyGivens Performing Arts CenterGlobal EngagementGraduate School, TheHandshakeHealth Careers Access ProgramHEALTH CommitteeHealth Sciences, College of Healthy Start CORPSHistoryHonors CollegeHousing and Residence LifeHuman ResourcesInformation Technology (DoIT)Institutional ResearchInstitutional Review BoardInteractive Video FacilityInterdisciplinary StudiesInternal AuditJones CenterKinesiologyLibraryLicensureMass CommunicationMathematics and Computer ScienceMBA ProgramMPA ProgramMilitary Science (Army ROTC)Museum of the Southeast American IndianMusicNC PromiseNursingOnline Learning, Office ofOrientation, FreshmanParent & Family EngagementPhilosophy and ReligionPine Needle, ThePURC CenterPolice and Public SafetyPolicies & RegulationsPolitical Science and Public AdministrationPrint ServicesPsychologyPurchasingQuality Enhancement PlanRISERegional Initiatives, Office forRegistrarSexual Assault/Sexual HarassmentSocial WorkSociology and Criminal JusticeSoutheast American Indian Studies ProgramSponsored Research and ProgramsStaff CouncilStudent AccountsStudent AffairsStudent ConductStudent HandbookStudent Health ServicesStudent Inclusion and DiversityStudent Learning OutcomesStudy AbroadSummer SchoolSustainabilityTRIO ProgramsTeacher Education ProgramsTeaching and Learning CenterTheatre, UniversityThomas Entrepreneurship HubTitle IX & Clery ComplianceUniversity Center & ProgramsUniversity Communications & MarketingUniversity School Partnerships and Clinical PracticeUniversity Writing CenterWNCP RadioWNCP-TV
Popular Links
Calendar, Academic
Calendar, University
Campus Directory
Campus Map
Catalog, Academic
Dining Services
Library
Bookstore
Send CARE Referral
Emergency Information
Active Shooter Info
Choosetobeabrave.com
Account Logins
Banner (faculty/staff)
BraveConnect
BraveMail
BraveWeb
BraveCart
BraveCart Shopper
Canvas
Chrome River Travel
Curriculog
EAB Navigate
Facilities Reservation System
Facilities Work Request
Handshake
ITSM Self Service (HEAT)
Office 365
OWA (faculty/staff)
WebEx (faculty/staff/students)
Zoom (faculty/staff/students)
Important Updates about COVID-19
Read more about UNCP's response to COVID-19. STUDENTS: click here to apply for CARES funding today!
Main navigation
Menu
ABOUT
About the Community
Administration
Campus Map
Campus Resources
Chancellor
ADMISSIONS
Why UNC Pembroke?
Undergraduate Admissions
Graduate Admissions
Continuing Education
Military Affiliated Students
Important Dates
Costs and Financial Aid
Cost Calculator
Registrar
Legal, Copyright & Privacy
UNC Pembroke encourages those affiliated with the university to make full, appropriate use of the World Wide Web. However, the university cannot guarantee the accuracy or completeness of the information published or stored on the UNCP website. The university is not liable for any damages of any kind arising from the submission, installation, maintenance, transmission, copying, modification, distribution or use of any materials on the site. Nor is UNCP responsible for errors of information provided on the sites; the materials are provided "as is" without warranties of any kind. Thus, the information should not be used as an exclusive basis for decision making.
UNC Pembroke does not guarantee that the site will function error free or uninterrupted or that loss of privacy, theft of information, damage or loss of data arising directly or indirectly from the absence or failure of security protection mechanisms will not occur.
Thus, UNCP cannot be held liable for any consequence of placing sensitive information on the website. Those storing information on the UNCP website represent and warrant to UNCP that the installation, copying, distribution and use of such materials in connection with the UNCP website will not violate any other party's proprietary rights; nor does this information contain libelous or defamatory statements. Information on group or personal web pages does not constitute official university content, nor sponsorship of content. The views and opinions expressed are strictly those of the page authors, to whom comments and questions should be addressed.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. A User’s Web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Users may choose to set their Web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert them when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
The University of North Carolina at Pembroke may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
To provide services to the UNCP community and to serve other university needs;
To improve constituent service;
To respond to service requests and support needs more efficiently;
To personalize user experience;
Using aggregated information to understand how our Users leverage resources provided on Site;
To run a promotion, survey or other Site feature;
To improve content and functionality of Site;
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them; and
To send periodic emails.
We may use the email address to respond to inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If a User decides to opt-in to any mailing list of UNCP contained on the Site, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third-party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.
Third-party partner: Capture Higher Ed
UNC Pembroke may partner with third parties to assist in better understanding how users interact with content on this Site. These partners help us enhance our marketing efforts. For more information about Capture's privacy policy, please read: Capture privacy policy.
Web Accessibility
UNCP’s webpages form a living document and are regularly updated. We strive to make our website universally accessible. Please contact the webmaster if you experience accessibility difficulties with specific content.
For more information, contact the university web publisher at 910.521.6820 or web@uncp.edu.
About Us
About Menu (levels 2+)
